A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 3
  - King Faisal Award (Box 80, Folder 545)
  - Kln (Box 80, Folder 546)
  - Krim, Interferon, 1983 May (Box 80, Folder 547)
  - Kringles (Box 80, Folder 548)
  - Lasker Award (Box 80, Folder 549-550)
  - Lasker Award Programs, 1975; 1989 (Box 81, Folder 551)
  - Lerner Letters and Plans and Written Materials (Box 81, Folder 552)
  - Lin, Glucagon (Box 81, Folder 553)
  - Loew, Gilda (Box 81, Folder 554)
  - Macauley, Cyclic Glucagon (Box 81, Folder 555)
  - Macromolecular Structure Committee and Cell Biology (Search Committee, Promotion Evaluation Committee) (Box 81, Folder 556)
  - Magainin (Box 81, Folder 557-558, Box 82, Folder 559-561, Box 83, Folder 562)
  - Mailing Lists (Box 83, Folder 563)
  - Manning, Maury, Vasopressin (Box 83, Folder 564)
  - Maps (Box 83, Folder 565)
  - Mass Spec. (Spectrometry) - Glucagon (Box 83, Folder 566)
  - Mass Spectrometer (Box 83, Folder 567)
  - Mass Spectrometry (Box 83, Folder 568)
  - Materials on Genome Project, Innate Ab (Box 83, Folder 569)
  - Membranes (Box 84, Folder 570)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 84, Folder 571-573)
  - Merrifield Symposium, 1999-2001 (Box 84, Folder 574)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Additions for the Expanded Video, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 575)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Aftermath and Responses, 2001-2005 (Box 85, Folder 576)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Andreu, David, 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 577)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Bibliographies, 1963-2000 (Box 85, Folder 578)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Comments for Revisions of the Video, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 579)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Contributions to the Video, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 580)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Cosand, Wes, 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 581)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Expenses Charged to Video Account, 2001-2007 (Box 85, Folder 582)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Felix, Art, 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 583)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Final Changes in the Video, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 584)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Mailing List, 2000-2003 (Box 85, Folder 585)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Narrator and RBM, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 586)
  - Merrifield Symposium, New Material and Additions for Video, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 587)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Photolithography, Diagrams, and Illustrations, Media Service Work, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 588)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Reprints, 1965-2000 (Box 86, Folder 589)
  - Merrifield Symposium, RU Account, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 590)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Satellite Symposium, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 591)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Script, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 592)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Script Version II E, 2001 September (Box 86, Folder 593)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Showing the Video at RU, 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 594)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Video Account Statements, 2001-2006 (Box 86, Folder 595)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Video Budgets, 1999-2001 (Box 86, Folder 596)
  - Merrifield Symposium, Work and Expenses on Expanded Version of Video, 2001-2002 (Box 86, Folder 597)
  - Merrifield Tribute, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 598)
  - Merrifield Tribute, Unlabeled Folder, 1977-2007 (Box 86, Folder 599-600, Box 87, Folder 601-604)
  - Molecular Dynamics, Inc. (Box 87, Folder 605)
  - Monitor Method, NPIC (Box 87, Folder 606)
  - Monitoring Experiments (Box 87, Folder 607)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 87, Folder 608, Box 88, Folder 609-612)
  - National Academy of Sciences Meetings (Box 89, Folder 613)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, Sita, Carnegie Mellon University (Box 89, Folder 614)
  - Neurophysin (Box 89, Folder 615)
  - New Methods for Protecting Functional Groups, Erickson-Barany (Box 89, Folder 616)
  - New Solid Supports, Glass, New Resins (Box 89, Folder 617)
  - "News and Notes", 2001-2004 (Box 89, Folder 618)
  - Nirenberg Nomination (Box 89, Folder 619)
  - Nobel (Box 89, Folder 620)
  - Nobel Jubilee, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 621)
  - Nobel Prize (Box 90, Folder 622)
  - Nobel Prize, Rockefeller University Information (Box 90, Folder 623)
  - Notes on Melittin Action Papers and Other Peptides (Box 90, Folder 624)
  - N-Desacetylthymosin1 (Patent) (Box 90, Folder 625)
  - Office of Saline Water Grant Application, C.D. Tosteson, Duke University (Box 90, Folder 626)
  - pA2 (Box 90, Folder 627)
  - PACMVtetO-rat; PACMVtetO-human GR (Box 90, Folder 628)
  - Patent Serial No. 071546,845 (Box 90, Folder 629)
  - Patents, Agreements, etc. (Box 91, Folder 630)
  - Peptide and Protein Video (Box 91, Folder 631)
  - Peptide Sequencing Forms, 1987 March (Box 91, Folder 632)
  - Peptide Synthesis (Box 91, Folder 633)
  - Pharmaceutical Discovery Corporation (Box 91, Folder 634)
  - Photolytic Protecting Groups (Box 91, Folder 635)
  - Picower Institute for Medical Research (Box 91, Folder 636)
  - Pieczenik v. Dyax Corporation, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 637)
  - Pierce Award (Box 91, Folder 638)
  - Pierce Award Nominations (Box 92, Folder 639-642, Box 93, Folder 643)
  - Plastocyanin (Box 93, Folder 644)
  - PR-39 (Box 93, Folder 645)
  - Preview (Box 93, Folder 646)
  - Preview (Preview Sequences Analysis, PTH-Phenylthionhydantoin Amino Acids) (Box 93, Folder 647)
  - Problems Involving Solid Supports Resins; Affinity Chromatography; Supported Enzymes; Reagents (Box 93, Folder 648)
  - Profile Diagnostic Services (Box 93, Folder 649-650, Box 94, Folder 651)
  - Properties of Solid Supports (Box 94, Folder 652)
  - Proteases (Box 94, Folder 653)
  - Purification Synopsis for Cyclic Analog Peptides (Box 94, Folder 654)
  - Quench Correction Curves (Box 94, Folder 655)
  - Rabies (Box 94, Folder 656)
  - References for Cyclic Analog Paper (Box 95, Folder 65)
  - Reproductive Biology (Box 95, Folder 658-659)
  - Resin Reprints (Box 95, Folder 660)
  - Resins: Swelling, Intersite, Reprints (Box 96, Folder 661)
  - Retro Melittin (Box 96, Folder 662)
  - Retro-enantio CA - Me (Box 96, Folder 663)
  - Ribonuclease Inhibitor (Box 96, Folder 664)
  - Ribonuclease Reviews and Papers and Notes (Box 96, Folder 665)
  - Roche (Box 97, Folder 666-669, Box 98, Folder 670)
  - Rockefeller University (Box 98, Folder 671)
  - Rockefeller University, 75th Reunion (Box 98, Folder 672)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council (Box 98, Folder 673)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council (Box 98, Folder 673A)
  - Rockefeller University Academic Council (Box 99, Folder 674-675)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council and Senate (Box 99, Folder 676)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council and Senate (Box 99, Folder 676A)
  - Rockefeller University, Administration, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 677)
  - Rockefeller University, Biochem Course (Box 99, Folder 678-679)
  - Rockefeller University, Biochemistry Exams (Box 99, Folder 680)
  - Rockefeller University, Business (Box 99, Folder 681)
  - Rockefeller University, Calendars, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 682)
  - Rockefeller University, Chemical Sciences Committee (Box 100, Folder 683)
  - Rockefeller University, Chemistry Seminar Series (Box 100, Folder 684)
  - Rockefeller University, Committee on Organic Chemistry and Biochemistry (Box 100, Folder 685)
  - Rockefeller University, Committee on Organic Chemistry and Biochemistry, 1965-1978 (Box 100, Folder 686-691, Box 101, Folder 692)
  - Rockefeller University, Convocation (Box 101, Folder 693)
  - Rockefeller University, Dean of Students (Box 101, Folder 694)
  - Rockefeller University, Dean of Students (Box 101, Folder 694A)
  - Rockefeller University, Faculty Club (Box 101, Folder 695)
  - Rockefeller University, Faculty Committee on Lectures (Box 101, Folder 696)
  - Rockefeller University, FY06 Budget (Box 101, Folder 697)
  - Rockefeller University, Goldberg, Allan, Promotion (Box 101, Folder 698)
  - Rockefeller University, Goldberg, Allan, Promotion (Box 101, Folder 698A)
  - Rockefeller University, Honorary Degrees, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 699)
  - Rockefeller University, Institute Announcements, Pre-1969 (Box 102, Folder 700)
  - Rockefeller University, Judicial Committee (Box 102, Folder 701)
  - Rockefeller University, Laboratory Animal Research Center (Box 102, Folder 702)
  - Rockefeller University, Laboratory Safety (Box 102, Folder 703)
  - Rockefeller University, Lecture Committee (Box 102, Folder 704-706, Box 103, Folder 707-709)
  - Rockefeller University, Lecture Committee, Lectures (Box 103, Folder 710-712)
  - Rockefeller University, Merrifield Laboratory Budget (Box 103, Folder 713)
  - Rockefeller University, NMR (Nuclear Magnetic Resonance) Laboratory (Box 103, Folder 714)
  - Rockefeller University, Nurse, Dr. Paul, Meeting, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 715)
  - Rockefeller University, Organic Chemistry at Rockefeller University (Box 104, Folder 716)
  - Rockefeller University, Painting, Secretary's Office, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 717)
  - Rockefeller University, Peptide Seminars, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 718)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, A-B (Box 104, Folder 719)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, C-D (Box 104, Folder 720)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, E-G (Box 104, Folder 721)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, H-I (Box 105, Folder 722)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, J-K (Box 105, Folder 723)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, L (Box 105, Folder 724)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, M (Box 105, Folder 725)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, N-P (Box 105, Folder 726)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, Q-R (Box 105, Folder 727)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, S (Box 106, Folder 728)
  - Rockefeller University, Photograph Directory, T-Z (Box 106, Folder 729)
  - Rockefeller University, Program in Reproductive Biology, Progress Report, 1972-1973 (Box 106, Folder 730)
  - Rockefeller University, Publications, 1969-1970 (Box 106, Folder 731)
  - Rockefeller University, Research Colloquia Abstracts (Box 106, Folder 732)
  - Rockefeller University, Restructuring the Rockefeller University Faculty, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 733)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1949-1956 (Box 106, Folder 734)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefeller Institute Quarterly (Box 107, Folder 735)
  - Rockefeller University, Safety Committee (Box 107, Folder 736)
  - Rockefeller University, Scientific and Educational Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 737)
  - Rockefeller University, Sponsored Programs Funding Guide (Box 107, Folder 738)
  - Rockefeller University, Stock Orders (Box 107, Folder 739-740)
  - Rockefeller University, Submitted Questions, Biochem Exam (Box 107, Folder 741)
  - Rockefeller University, Travel Policies (Box 108, Folder 742)
  - Rockefeller University, University Announcements, Services (Box 108, Folder 743)
  - Rockefeller University, University Business (Box 108, Folder 744)
  - Rockefeller University, University Business, Promotions, New Appointments (Box 108, Folder 745)
  - Rockefeller University, University Business, Promotions, New Appointments (Box 108, Folder 746)
  - RV Act. and Conc. Files Used for Peptide Syntheses: Cycamide (Box 108, Folder 747)
  - Satyam Data on CPI and PR39 (Box 108, Folder 748)
  - Schwarz BioResearch (Box 108, Folder 749)
  - Scintillation (Box 108, Folder 750)
  - Scintillation Counter (Box 108, Folder 751)
  - Selectide Corporation (Box 108, Folder 752, Box 109, Folder 753-756)
  - Skin Disease Society (Box 109, Folder 757)
  - Slide Material, Glucagon (Box 110, Folder 758)
  - Solid Phase Synthesis of Sperm Whale Myoglobin (Box 110, Folder 759)
  - Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis, Glucagon (Box 110, Folder 760)
  - Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis, Old SPPS Data (Box 110, Folder 761)
  - Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis, Summaries of Early Experiments on Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis (Box 110, Folder 762)
  - Stable Peptide Kappa Opioid Receptor Agonists (E-2078) (Box 110, Folder 763)
  - Statistical Analysis (Box 110, Folder 764)
  - Sulfmoc (Box 110, Folder 765, Box 111, Folder 766)
  - Svetlana (Mojsov), Glucagon, 1983 August 8 (Box 111, Folder 767)
  - Svetlana (Mojsov), Glucagon (Box 111, Folder 768)
  - Sweeteners, Weinshenker (Box 111, Folder 769)
  - Synthesizers (Box 111, Folder 770)
  - Synthetic Antigens, 2Hydroxybenzyl AHs (Box 111, Folder 771)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Allyl Esters and Amides Palor (Box 111, Folder 772)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Arbuzov, Phosphonates, Phosphonamidates (Box 111, Folder 773)
  - Synthetic Antigens, HPLC Runs (Box 111, Folder 774)
  - Synthetic Antigens, NMR Data (Box 112, Folder 775)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Notes and Data and Plans before Notebook except NMR and HPLC (Box 112, Folder 776)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Notes, Plans, and Procedures (Box 112, Folder 777)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Summaries of Syntheses (Box 112, Folder 778)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Unlabeled Folder (Box 112, Folder 779)
  - Taniguchi Fibroblast Intereron (Box 112, Folder 780)
  - Thymosin (Box 112, Folder 781)
  - Thymosin, Patent (Box 112, Folder 782)
  - To Read (Box 112, Folder 783)
  - Trimethylsilyl (Box 113, Folder 784)
  - TRP (for) (Box 113, Folder 785)
  - Trypsin Inhibitor (Box 113, Folder 786)
  - [Tyr22] Glucagon, Gui Shen (Box 113, Folder 787)
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 113, Folder 788-790)
    Includes: The Rockefeller University Convocation Program, 1993 "125I-labeled Crosslinking Reagent that is Hydrophilic, Photoactivatable, and Cleavable through an Azo Linkage" by Denny and Blobel "Structural Transformations During Chloromethylation of Flexible Polystyrene Networks" by Belfer, Glozman, Deshe, and Warshawsky "Structure-Activity Relations of Conotoxins at the Neuromuscular Junction" by Hashimoto, Uchida, Yoshida, Sakakibara, and Yukari "Structure-Activity Study of -Human Atrial Natriuretic Polypeptide (-hANP)" by Chino, Nishiuchi, Noda, Watanabe, Kimura, and Sakakibara "Solution Synthesis of Porcine, Human and Bovine Gastric Inhibitory Polypeptides" by Kumagaye, Chino, Nishiuchi, Kuroda, Kimura, and Sakakibara "Synthesis of -Conotoxin GVIA with Three Intramolecular Disulfide Bridges" by Nishiuchi, Kumagaye, Noda, Watanabe, and Sakakibara "Total Synthesis of S-Carbamoylmethyl Bovine Apocytochrome C by Segment Coupling" by Blake The Rockefeller University, Report of the President, 1980 & 1981 "Scientific Instruments," Caspary Gallery of The Rockefeller University, 1976 "Temperature Induced Chromatographic Selectivity in Reversed-Phase Peptide Analysis (2D-HPLC/Insulin/Conformational Analysis)" by DiMarchi and Long The Rockefeller University Convocation Program, 1982 "Scientific Instruments," Caspary Gallery of The Rockefeller University "Anti--interferon Antibodies Inhibit the Increased Expression of HLA-B7 mRNA in Tumor Necrosis Factor-Treated Human Fibroblasts: Structural Studies of the 2 Interferon Involved" by May, Helfgott, and Sehgal Patent Interference no. 100,787 "Reutilization of Fatty Acid Carbons for Lung Lipid Synthesis" by Rabinowitz, Cardwell, and Bassett "Fatty Acid Metabolism in Human Fetal Placental Vasculature" by Rulenko and Rabinowitz "12CO2 in Breath" by Rabinowitz and Lopez-Majano "Comparative Tissue Absorption of Oral 14C-Aspirin and Topical Triethanolamine 14C-Salicylate in Human and Canine Knee Joints" by Rabinowitz, Feldman, Weinberger, and Schumacher "Lipid Composition of Human Dental Pulp" by Rabinowitz and Rossman "Lipid Composition of the Tissues of Human Knee Joints" by Rabinowitz, Gregg, Nixon, and Schumacher "Lipid Composition and de novo Lipid Biosynthesis of Human Palmar Fat in Dupuytren's Disease" by Rabinowitz, Ostermann, Bora, and Staeffen "A Method for Serum Octanoate in Hepatic Cirrhosis and Hepatic Encephalopathy" by Rabinowitz, Staeffen, Aumonier, Ballan, Ferrer, Terme, Series, and Myerson "Elongation of [-14C]Oleic Acid and [-14C]Nervonic Acid" by Rabinowitz, Lutton, and Chevallier "A Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Investigation of the Iodination of 1,2-Disubstituted Ethylenes, Evidence for a Trans Addition-Cis Elimination" by Zanger and Rabinowitz Wall Calendar, 1983 "Nobel Prize Laureates," 1985 "Peyton Rous Centennial: A Transmissable Avian Neoplasm (Sarcoma of the Common Fowl)," 1979 "A Tribute to Philip Handler, 1917-1981," 1982 "Libby, Willard Frank" "Semenov, Nikolai Nickolaevich" "Programme of United States-Republic of China Binational Seminar on Protein Chemistry, Snake Venom and Hormonal Proteins," 1976 "Adolph C. and Mary Sprague Miller Institute for Basic Research in Science, 1955-1980: Twenty-Five Year Report" by Cohen "Detlev Wulf Bronk, 1897-1975" by Brink, Jr.
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 114, Folder 791-794)
    Includes: "Modification of Peptides Containing Glutamic Acid by Hydrogen Fluoride-Anisole Mixtures. -Acylation of Anisole or the Glutamyl Nitrogen" by Feinberg and Merrifield "Synthetic Position 5 Analogs of Adrenocorticotropin Fragments and Their in Vitro Lipolytic Activity" by Draper, Rizack, and Merrifield "Synthesis of a Hydrophobic Potassium Binding Peptide" by Gisin and Merrifield "Peptide Synthesis by Means of tert-Butyloxycarbonylamino Acid Derivatives of Poly(ethylene-co-N-hydroxymaleimide" by Fridkin, Patchornik, and Katchalski "A Solid Phase-Fragment Approach to Peptide Synthesis" by Wang and Merrifield "Use of Chlorinated Benzyloxycarbonyl Protecting Groups to Eliminate N-Branching at Lysine during Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Erickson and Merrifield "Acid Stability of Several Benzylic Protecting Groups Used in Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis. Rearrangement of O-Benzyltyrosine to 3-Benzyltyrosine" by Erickson and Merrifield "Reactivation of des(119-, 120-, or 121-124) Ribonuclease A by Mixture with Synthetic COOH-terminal Peptides of Varying Lengths" by Gutte, Lin, Caldi, and Merrifield "Reactivation of des(119-124) Ribonuclease A by Mixture with Synthetic COOH-terminal Peptides; the Role of Phenylalanine-120" by Lin, Gutte, Caldi, Moore, and Merrifield "Preparation of Pancreatic Ribonucleases 1-114 and 1-115 and Their Reactivation by Mixture with Synthetic COOH-terminal Peptides" by Hayashi, Moore, and Merrifield "Substrate Specificity of a Histone Deacetylase from Calf Thymus Nuclei" by Kreiger, Levine, Merrifield, Vidali, and Allfrey "Lipolytic Activity of Met-Arg-His-Phe-Arg-Trp-Gly, a Synthetic Analog of the ACTH (4-10) Core Sequence" by Draper, Merrifield, and Rizack "Stability of Side-Chain Protecting Groups in Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Erickson and Merrifield "Solid Phase Synthesis of Bovine Pituitary Growth Homrone-(123-131) Nonapeptide" by Wang, Yang, Kulesha, Sonenberg, and Merrifield "A Synthetic Study of the Effect of Tyrosine at Position 120 of Ribonuclease" by Hodges and Merrifield "Zinc Chloride-Catalyzed Chloromethylation of Resins for Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Feinberg and Merrifield "Scientific Instruments," Caspary Gallery of The Rockefeller University, 1976"Studies on the Total Synthesis of an Enzyme. V. Thepreparation of Enzymatically Active Material" "Solid-State NMR Structural Studies of Peptides and Proteins in Membranes" by Cross and Opella "Mechanisms and Prevention of Trifluoroacetylation in Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Kent, Mitchell, Engelhard, and Merrifield "Opioid Activity of Synthetic and Naturally Occuring Enkephalin Peptides" by Simon, Bonnet, Hiller, Reiman, and Merrifield "The Synthesis of Diacetylated Histone H4-(1-37) for Studies on the Mechanism of Histone Deacetylation" by Kreiger, Vidali, Erickson, Allfrey, and Merrifield "Cyclohexyl Ester as a New Protecting Group for Aspartyl Peptides to Minimize Aspartimide Formation in Acidic and Basic Treatments" by Tam, Wong, Riemen, Tjoeng, and Merrifield "Second Alan E. Pierce Award Lecture" by Merrifield "Quantitative Determination of D- and L-Amino Acids by Reaction with tert-Butyloxycarbonyl-L-leucine N-Hydroxycuccinimide Ester and Chromatographic Separation as L,D and L,L Dipeptides" by Mitchell, Kent, Chu, and Merrifield "Tyrosine Protecting Groups: Minimization of Rearrangement to 3-Alkyltyrosine during Acidolysis" by Engelhard and Merrifield "Test for Racemization in Model Peptide Synthesis by Direct Chromatographic Separation of Diastereomers of the Tetrapeptide Leucylalanylglycylvaline" by Kent, Mitchell, Barany, and Merrifield "9-(2-Sulfo)fluorenylmethyloxycarbonyl Chloride, a New Reagent for the Purification of Synthetic Peptides" by Merrifield and Bach "Preparation and Properties of tert-Butyloxycarbonylaminoacyl-4-(oxymethyl) phenylacetamidomethyl-(Kel F-g-styrene) Resin, an Insoluble, Noncrosslinked Support for Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Kent and Merrifield "The Limits of Reaction of Radioactive Dicyclohexylcarbodiimide with N-Amino Groups during Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Merrifield, Gisin, and Bach "Concept of Internal Structural Controls for Evaluation of Inactive Synthetic Peptide Analogs: Synthesis of [Orn13,14]apamin and its Guanidination to an Apamin Derivative with Full Neurotoxic Activity" by Cosand and Merrifield "The Role of Serine-123 in the Activity and Specificity of Ribonuclease" by Hodges and Merrifield "Occurrence of N-Alkylation during the Acidolytic Cleavage of Urethane Protecting Groups" by Mitchell and Merrifield "The -Phenacyl Ester as a Temporary Protecting Group to Minimize Cyclic Imide Formation during Subsequent Treatment of Aspartyl Peptides with HF" by Yang and Merrifield "Preparation of Aminomethyl-Polystyrene Resin by Direct Amidomethylation" by Mitchell, Kent, Erickson, and Merrifield
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 115, Folder 795-799)